nammadasnaikiri r@gmail.com	~
.02222 2000711	г

House No. R-36, A-One Cottages Block-9, Federal B Area, Karachi, Pakistan

I have worked steadily throughout university and after completion of my studies, gaining valuable experience that equips me to present a firm with advantages others may not offer. At the moment I strongly desire to gain professional experience in a reputable organization which provides ample learning opportunities so that I can further enhance my personal and professional skills as well as polish upon the existing ones.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Supply Chain Executive Zara Mobility Services

08/2016 - Present Karachi

Tasks

- Managing Company's serialized and Non-serialized inventory. This includes optimization of inventory levels and standardization of materials specifications.
- Allocate workload ensuring effective delivery of a high quality support to Business Units.
- Primary point of contact between both (Company and the Vendor).
- Manage the ordering and receipt of products including submitting purchase requisitions.
- Maintained computerized record of all products.
- Oversee routine operational activities of Stock Management ensuring that assets & equipment's are fully functional, stocks levels & inventory movements are reviewed/monitored against planned data.
- Prepare weekly, monthly, quarterly and annual reports to analyze future sales & demand.
- Collaborate with inventory team to streamline processes and improve in-time supply
- Track, verify and reconcile use of supplies to maintain 100 percent accounting of stock.
- Maintain all relevant inventory paperwork and entered accurate inventory data in computer system.

Administration Officer

GCS Pvt Ltd

03/2015 - 10/2015 Karachi

- Tasks
- Manage phone calls and correspondence (e-mail, letters, packages
- Track stocks of office supplies and place orders when necessary.
- Maintaining a clean and working environment.
- Organizing, arranging and coordinating meetings.
- Sorting and distributing incoming and outgoing post.

EDUCATION

Bachelors in Business Administration

Igra University

01/2013 - 12/2017

Intermediate

hamdard college of science & commerce

2009 - 2011

